Charles Mingus Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Writings (Box 49-53)
  - Writings About CM (Box 47, Box 50-53)
    - Newsletters, Press Releases, & Bulletins (Box-folder 47/14)
      - Atlantic/Atco
      - Committee for Artistic Freedom
      - Corriere Della Sera
      - Jazz Workshop
      - The Merlin Group
      - New Audiences
      - Philharmonic Hall
      - Truno e Della
  - Miscellaneous Writings (Box 48)
    - Film Work
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 48/1)
      - Scripts and Related Material
        - A song with orange in it, by S. Lee Pogostin; Robert Herridge, producer [script; 2 copies, 1 copy incomplete] (Box-folder 48/2)
        - Frankie and Johnnie, adapted for television by Lee Sherman; Robert Herridge, producer [annotated script]
        - Sierra Nevada, by Elio Petri; Daniele Senatore, producer [production summary; 2 copies, Copy 1 bound] (Box-folder 48/3)
        - Zoo, by Elio Petri; Daniele Senatore, producer [story synopsis, production summary, and miscellaneous]
        - [Untitled screenplay], by John Byron, Edward Pressman, producer [script] (Box-folder 48/4)
    - Poetry (Box-folder 48/5)
      - "Blues for Eric Dolphy", by John Sinclair
      - "Dreams, things, and offsprings", by Eric V. Tait, Jr.
      - Four poems for Charles Mingus, by Lyon Phelps
        - "Audience"
        - "Box office"
        - "Lament for Saturday night"
        - "On the stand"
    - Short stories (Box-folder 48/6)
      - Angel baby, by Jack Micheline
      - Waiting for Sam, by Marian Ungerer
    - Miscellany (Box-folder 48/7)
- Business Papers (Box 54-64)
  The Business Papers Series consists of Charles Mingus headed three music business ventures Charles Mingus Enterprises, Inc.; Debut Records; and the Jazz Workshop, Inc.
  Business Papers series is arranged as follows:
  Contracts, arranged chronologically by date.
  Correspondence, arranged alphabetically by name then chronologically by date.
  Invoices, receipts and statements, arranged alphabetically by vender name then chronologically by date.
  Royalty statements, arranged alphabetically by company name, then alphabetically by artist name, then chronologically by date.
  - Brande Boghandel: Debut Records, Brande, Denmark (Box-folder 54/1)
    - Contract
    - Correspondence
    - Invoices
    - Royalty statements
    - Miscellaneous
  - Charles Mingus Enterprises / Chaz-Mar Music
    - Contracts (Box-folder 54/2)
    - Correspondence Received: Corporate
      - Albert Shultz, Inc. (Box-folder 54/3)
        - Atsidis, Stanley
      - American Dance Festival
        - Reinhart, Charles
      - American Federation of Musicians
        - Ballard, Stanley
        - Clancy, George V.
        - Crothers, Robert
        - Davis, Hal C.
        - Ritacco, Tina
      - Ampex Corporation
        - Brusso, Irv
      - Argus South African Newspapers Ltd.
        - Wentzel, A.
      - Associated Booking Corp.
        - Archer, Jack
        - Glaser, Joe
        - Green, Jack L.
        - Silber, Marcia
      - Associated Musicians of New York
        - Arons, Max L.
        - Critelli, Louis
        - Jaffe, Hy
      - Atlantic Recording Corporation
        - Donovan, Norah
      - Auto Baby Sitters of New York
        - Schiffman, N.
      - BMI (Broadcast Music, Inc.) (Box-folder 54/4)
        - Fabbio, Patrick J.
        - Feilich, Al
        - Marlo, George M.
        - Paesler, Peter C.
      - Bakers Keyboard Lounge
        - [no individual specified]
      - Berkley High Jazz Club
        - Sacks, Andy
      - Bernard Geis Associates
        - Pogrebin, Letty Cottin
      - Bethlehem Music Corporation
        - Knockelman, Gladys
      - Better Business Bureau of Metropolitan New York, Inc.
        - Godreau, P.J.
      - Civic Publications, Inc. (Box-folder 54/4)
        - Stokes, Sylvia
      - Columbia Records
        - Macero, Teo
        - Corblavan, Inc.
        - Leon, L.
      - Cornell University: College of Arts and Sciences
        - Austin, William W.
      - Decca Record Company Limited
        - Norris, E.A.
      - Eltron Export Company
        - Glover, W.T.
      - Fairmont Hotel and Tower (Box-folder 54/5)
        - Thompson, J.
      - Fantasy Records, Inc.
        - Welbourn, Betty
        - Zaentz, Celia
      - Festival Productions Inc.
        - Wein, George T.
      - Fleet Services Incorporated
        - Estrow, Julius
      - Grand Parade du Jazz
        - Wein, George T.
      - H.M. Inspector of Taxes
        - Cropper, E.
        - Stanton, D.H.
        - White, G.W.
      - Harold Davison, Ltd.
        - Tobutt, D.
      - Harry Fox Agency, Inc.
        - [no individual specified]
      - Inland Revenue (Box-folder 54/6)
        - Evans, G.
      - Inquisition Coffee House
        - Bateman, Howie
      - International Jazz Festival
        - Doruzka, Lubomir
      - Japabooking
        - [no individual specified]
      - Jazz Journal International
        - Jeske, Lee
      - JazzYatra 78
        - Jhaveri, Niranjan
      - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation
        - Ray, Gordon M.
        - Schlesinger, Stephen L.
      - Joseph S. Carlitz Chemists
        - Carlitz, Kay
      - Karpatkin & Karpatkin
        - Karpatkin, Marvin M.
      - Kaybank Recording Corporation
        - Becky, J.
      - Ken Mayer Associates (Box-folder 54/6)
        - Mayer, Ken
      - Lone Star Publishing Co., Inc.
        - Islar, Albert H.
      - MacPherson Travel Bureau, Inc.
        - "Jeanne"
      - Madison Press Club
        - Burke, Jack
      - McGraw-Hill, Inc.
        - Saunders, Paul
      - Monterey Jazz Festival
        - Lyons, James L.
      - Musical Union of Baltimore City
        - McElfresh, Charles W.
      - Musicians' Protective Union
        - Gwynn, Charles E.
      - Musidisc-Europe
        - Berjot, Pierre
      - Nason & Cohen (Box-folder 54/7)
        - Nason, Herbert
      - Newport Jazz Festival
        - "Margot"
        - Wein, George
      - Office de Radiodiffusion-Télévision Française
        - Malson, Lucien
      - Philadelphia Civic Center
        - Newborn, Edward
      - Playboy
        - Solomon, Dave
        - Snyder, Carl
      - Polo Warehouse & Storage Corp.
        - Cucinella, Joseph
      - The Quiet Knight [night club]
        - [name not distinguishable]
      - Rank Organization of Canada Limited
        - Lawson, Frank
      - Schott Frères
        - Junne, J.J.
      - Shaw Artists Corporation
        - Whittemore, Jack
      - Smith College
        - Coffey, Ana
      - Société Française de Concerts
        - Tronchot, Jean
      - Swedish Broadcasting Corp.
        - Geis, Bernard
      - Tom Copi Photos
        - Copi, Tom
      - Town Hall
        - Leeds, Candace
      - United States Information Agency
        - Anderson, Constance M.
      - Walker Art Center (Box-folder 54/7)
        - Geffen, Don
      - Wells Fargo Bank
        - Flood, James
      - Western Union Telegraph Company
        - Connelly, F.J.
      - Willard Alexander, Inc.
        - Dinkin, Irv
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 54/8)
    - Correspondence Received: Individuals
      - Atkinson, Richard H. (Box-folder 54/9)
      - Beckwith, Steve & Leslie
      - Bekins, Jack Gray
      - Beltley, Christain, Jr.
      - Bendich, Albert M.
      - Bishop, Robert O.
      - Boriskin, Kim A.
      - Braley, Jean B.
      - Burrrows, Carmen
      - Davis, Clive
      - Caviola, Gaetan
      - Cawley, Margaret
      - Chaplin, John M., Jr.
      - Comuccini, Jody
      - Cosgrove, Raymond
      - Cronin, George Richard
      - Cross, David E.
      - Davis, Clive J.
      - De Maro, Andrew
      - Delinski, Harold
      - Easton, Robert
      - Easton, Sharon
      - Evalt, George J., Jr.
      - Evans, Irvin
      - Farrow, N.H. (Box-folder 54/10)
      - Fischer, Howard E.
      - Frances, Helene
      - Gavioli, Giordano
      - Gerke, Sherman
      - Gerstein, Marvin
      - Giusti, Calvin V.
      - Glaser, Joe
      - Grabo, Frederick H.
      - Grauer, Ben
      - Green, Jack L.
      - Halford, Steve
      - Harrison, Denis M.
      - Hawkins, G.T.
      - Hazell, C. Vaughn
      - Heinz, L.
      - Hiken, Sidney U.
      - Homes, Mike
      - Humphreys, Graham (Box-folder 54/10)
      - Ingham, Hepburn (Box-folder 54/11)
      - Jackson, Gwendolyn
      - Johnson, William W.
      - Jucker, Franco
      - Judd, Robert D.
      - Junne, J.J.
      - Kemsey, Joseph
      - Kobler, U.
      - Kostial, Walter
      - Kraner, Dietrich H.
      - Kyrou, Ado
      - Lamb, Curtis
      - Lee, Calvin M., Jr.
      - Levy, Robert B.
      - Loewenthal, M.
      - Lott, Alan
      - Lowe, T.
      - Mangus, Jackson P.
      - Marcus, Maxine H.
      - "Mason"
      - Matthews, D.R.
      - McCoy, Donald
      - McDonnell, Pat
      - McIntyre, V.E.
      - McKinney, William S.
      - McNally, Paul C.
      - Mietzel, Michael J.
      - Moulton, James C.
      - O'Connor, C.J. (Box-folder 54/12)
      - Palma, Don
      - Patterson, Kathleen
      - Pendzich, Edward
      - Petersen, Charles E.
      - Pierpaoli, Mike
      - Piersol, William A.
      - Quersin, Benoit
      - Raff, Robin C.
      - Rattners, Lewis
      - Richmond, Dannie
      - Riddell, Ronald C.
      - Roth, Carl R.
      - Sabin, Ruth B.
      - Sales, Grover, Jr.
      - Sanford, Alpheus
      - Schenker, Heinz
      - Schütte, Franz
      - Scott, Bettie Sue
      - Setterberg, Fred S.
      - Smith, J.O.
      - Stateler, Lloyd
      - Stolaski, M.J.
      - Struggles, Kirk (Box-folder 54/12)
      - Sutherland, Frances E.
      - Taylor, Howard
      - Tiller, F.M.
      - Tonsberg, Finn
      - Tucker, Tom R.
      - Walton, Ruth
      - Ward, David J.
      - Warner, Ross
      - Warren, Alan
      - Weete, Carol E.
      - Wehr, C.H.
      - Weitermann, Bruce R.
      - Werner, Uehlinger
      - Westmoreland, Barbara
      - Williams, Denis J.
      - Wood, Thomas P.
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 54/13)
    - Correspondence Sent: Corporate (Box-folder 54/14)
      - ABC Records
        - Graham, Susan
      - American Federation of Musicians
        - Mabry, Frank
      - Associated Musicians of Greater New York
        - Mabry, Frank
      - Columbia Records
        - Mingus, Charles
      - Coral Studios
        - Ungaro, Sasan Graham
      - Cornell University
        - Francis, Muriel
      - Department of Relocation, New York City
        - Mingus, Charles
      - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation
        - Graham, Susan
        - Mingus, Charles
      - H.N. Inspector of Taxes
        - Mingus, Charles
      - King Records, Inc.
        - Morea, Dominick
      - Lee King & Partner, Inc. (Box-folder 54/14)
        - [no individual specified]
      - Savoy Record Co., inc.
        - Ferris, M.
      - S.P.P.
        - Mingus, Charles
      - United Artists
        - Mingus, Charles
    - Correspondence Sent: Individuals (Box-folder 54/15)
      - Chachere, Marvin
      - Geis, Bernard
      - Guy, Warner
      - Jones, Morty (Box-folder 54/15)
      - Jones, Robert
      - Kunst, Johan
      - Kyrou, Ado
      - Mabry, Frank
      - Pogrebin, Bertrand B.
      - Roach, Max
      - Roo, Joop de
      - Preston, Eddie
      - Shemel, Sidney
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 54/16)
    - General Services: Vender Sales and Services
      - Banking
        - Chemical Corn Exchange Bank (Box-folder 54/17)
          - Cancelled checks
          - Statements
          - Miscellaneous
        - First National City Bank (Box-folder 54/18)
          - Cancelled checks
          - Statements
          - Miscellaneous
        - Wells Fargo Bank (Box-folder 54/19)
          - Cancelled checks
          - Statements
          - Miscellaneous
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 54/20)
      - Miscellaneous invoices (Box-folder 54/21)
      - Miscellaneous receipts (Box-folder 54/22)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 54/23)
    - Inter-Office Business
      - Employee payments [receipts] (Box-folder 55/1)
      - Inter-office billing (Box-folder 55/2)
        - Office supplies
        - Miscellaneous
      - Legal file [affidavit and summons] (Box-folder 55/3)
      - Mailing/shipping (Box-folder 55/4)
        - Mail order requests
        - Miscellaneous ... see also Box 66
      - Receipt and release of lien forms (Box-folder 55/5)
      - Taxes (Box-folder 55/6)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 55/7)
    - Mechanical Licenses & Royalties
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 55/8)
      - Licenses (Box-folder 55/9)
    - Royalty statements
      - ABC-Paramount (Box-folder 55/10)
      - ABC Records
      - American Federation of Musicians (Box-folder 55/10)
      - Atlantic Records [(only] (Box-folder 55/11)
      - BMI (Broadcast Music, Inc.) [only] (Box-folder 55/12)
      - Bethlehem (Box-folder 55/10)
      - Cadence Records (Box-folder 55/13)
      - Columbia Records (CBS)
      - Decca Records
      - Keel Mfg. Corp.
      - McGraw-Hill Books
      - Mercury Records
      - Nordisk Copyright Bureau
      - Prestige Records
      - RCA Records
      - Savoy Music Co.
      - United Artists
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 55/14)
    - Music Supplies [miscellaneous] (Box-folder 55/15)
    - Promotional Material (Box-folder 55/16)
      - Charles Mingus Record Club ... see also Box 66
      - Concert announcements
      - Record catalogs
    - Tours and Concerts [on folders, Business Tours]
      - Iteneraries (Box-folder 55/17)
      - Laundry service (Box-folder 55/18)
      - Lodging [hotel receipts and statements] (Box-folder 55/19)
      - Meals (Box-folder 56/1)
      - Miscellaneous lists (Box-folder 56/2)
      - Musicians' payments [receipts and balance sheets] (Box-folder 56/3-5)
      - Technical riders (Box-folder 56/6)
      - Telephone [long distance] (Box-folder 56/7)
      - Travel expenses [receipts]
        - Airlines (Box-folder 56/8)
        - Private auto, limousine, and taxi (Box-folder 56/9)
        - Rail
      - Work permits (Box-folder 56/10)
        - Domestic
        - Foreign
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 57/1)
    - Miscellany (Box-folder 57/2)
  - Debut Records, Inc.
    - Company History (Box-folder 57/3)
    - Contracts (Box-folder 57/4)
    - Correspondence Received: Corporate
      - A/B Nordiska Musikförlaget (Box-folder 57/5)
        - [no individuals specified]
      - A & I Record Distributors
        - [no individuals specified]
      - Al Smith's Record Bar
        - Smith, Al
      - All Star Theatrical Agency
        - Friedman, Syd
      - American Press, Inc.
        - Klinefelter, H.E.
      - American Recordist Society
        - Kaplan, Max
      - Argyle Publishing Co. (Box-folder 57/5)
        - DeNotte, Warren
      - Billboard Publishing Co.
        - Ackerman, Paul
      - Birdland Record Shop
        - [name not distinguishable]
      - Bureau of Motor Vehicles
        - Goodman, Helen
      - Carl Cordover & Co.
        - Cordover, Carl
      - Catholic Preview of Entertainment, Inc.
        - Freehan, Eugene
      - Chemical Bank New York Trust
        - Gaffney, Clarence J.
      - Chemical Corn Exchange Bank
        - Taylor, Arthur P.
      - Cherokee Coal and Coke Co.
        - Stegall, Sydney H.
      - College Music Distributing Co.
        - "Audrey"
      - Columbia Music Company
        - Heller, Charles
      - Columbia Records
        - Avakian, George
      - Commercial Music Company
        - Strawhorn, Alice
      - Continental Assurance Company
        - Meyers, Ronald
      - D & D Distributing (Box-folder 57/6)
        - Maw, Dick
      - Dale Record Service
        - Dale, Harry
      - Decca Record Co., Ltd.
        - Hannicks, Raymond
      - Department Store Guide
        - Cushing, E. Mack
      - The Disc Shop
        - Bleicher, Fred
      - Dun & Bradstreet
        - Brockett, F.H.
        - Costa, E.
        - Mielbrecht, R.E.
      - East Coast Distributors
        - [no individual specified]
      - Elitco
        - [no individual specified]
      - Emperor Records
        - [name not distinquishable]
      - Florida Record and Appliance Company (Florida Record and Music Co.)
        - Ganong, Overton
      - Fortesque Jazz Club
        - Brown, John W.
      - Frumkin Sales Co., Inc. (Box-folder 57/6)
        - "H.F."
      - Gauls Book and Record Shop (Box-folder 57/7)
        - Bristol, Suzanne
      - Gillens Department Store
        - Westphal, Fred
      - Gray Manufacturing Co.
        - Freeman, Maury
      - Guy Ward Associates
        - Ward, Guy
      - Hal Faktor
        - Faktor, Hal
      - Hal-Mar Distributors
        - Kossoff, Hal
      - Har-Bock Music Co.
        - Bock, Richard
      - House of Music
        - Risner, Randolph
      - Jawood L. Anderson, Inc.
        - Evans, Jack W.
      - Jazz Diskothek
        - Braukmann, I.A.
      - Jazz Disques
        - Delaunay, Charles
      - Jazz Encyclopedia
        - Feather, Leonard
      - Jazzmania
        - Thiers, Walter
      - Jazz Monthly
        - McCarthy, Albert J.
      - Jazz Promotion, Inc.
        - Walker, Joseph M.
      - Jerry Marcus Showroom
        - Marcus, Jerry
      - J.R. Reed Music Co.
        - Fruth, Doris F.
      - Ken Paulsen Associates
        - Paulsen, Ken
      - KFMB Radio
        - Garland, Howard
      - KFRE - California Inland Broadcasting Co.
        - Hansen, Flo
      - KGES Radio
        - MacLeod, Dennis
      - KLAC Radio
        - Norman, Gene
      - KLUF Radio - "Music with Maggie"
        - Banks, Leon M. ("Maggie")
      - Knight Education, Inc.
        - Piraino, Mario J.
      - KUTA Radio
        - Zogg, Hal
      - Limelight Publications, Inc. (Box-folder 57/7)
        - Whitehorn, Chester
      - London Audio Centre
        - Aselstyne, John G.
      - Mademoiselle Magazine (Box-folder 57/8)
        - Sachs, Dorothy
      - Maher Publications, Inc.
        - Shilling, Peter
      - Mangold Distributing Co.
        - Goldberg, Mannie
      - Meade Music House
        - Anderson, N. Roaland
      - Melody Sales Co.
        - Davidson, R.H.
      - Melody Shop
        - Majors, Elsie
      - Microfusion, Inc.
        - Ketcham, Randy
      - Midwestern Music
        - [no individual specified]
      - The Modern Jazz Club
        - Rachilo, Solomon C.
      - Music Barn
        - Barber, Stephanie Frey
      - Music Craft Distributors of Hawaii
        - Kurokawa, Walter
      - Music Director
        - Chiaramonte, Al
      - Music International, Inc.
        - Reyes, B.
      - The Music Mart
        - [no individual specified]
      - Music-Please Co.
        - Hughes, Edward T.
      - The Music Shop
        - Frost, Harry
      - Music Suppliers of New England, Inc.
        - Carter, Harry
        - Trager, Eva
      - Musicians Mutual Protective Association
        - Morris, Don
      - Nelson Music House (Box-folder 57/9)
        - Tharalson, Bob
      - New Jazz Society of Toronto
        - Hoare, William S.
      - New Musical Express
        - Wright, Rachel
      - New York State Department of Labor
        - Green, Alfred L.
        - Wiener, Irving
      - Nichibei Center, Inc.
        - [name not distinguishable]
      - Norfolk Virginian-Pilot (Box-folder 57/9)
        - Foster, John
      - O Itaborahyense
        - Costa, Heitor
      - Odhams Press Ltd.
        - [name not distinguishable]
      - Opus Jazz
        - Antonissens, Rudolph
      - Pan Africa Company
        - Russell, E Joseph
      - Paprikás Weiss Importer
        - [no individual specified]
      - The Paterson Evening News
        - Greene, Abe J.
      - Persuasive Packaging Corp.
        - Lerner, Frank
      - Premeier Record Distributing Co.
        - [name not distinguishable]
      - Queen City Album Conpany (Box-folder 57/10)
        - Bosken, Edward R.
      - Radio 437 Store
        - Levin, Norman
      - Railway Express Agency
        - Cresson, E.W.
      - Rave Recording and Distributing Co.
        - Timmer, Joe
      - Record City
        - Schneider, S.B.
      - Record Hop, Inc.
        - Vartanian, Haik
      - Records, Inc.
        - Steen, C.H.
      - The Reporter
        - Tripp, Alice
      - Sam Goody at Snellenburgs
        - Langill, Warren A.
      - Savoy Record Company, Inc.
        - Gottesmann, H.
      - Schwann, Inc.
        - Strong, Carlton M.
      - Shaker Music Shop
        - Prendergast, James
      - Southern Music
        - Makela, Betty
      - Star Novelty Company
        - Karter, Phillip
      - State University of New York College for Teachers
        - Tallmadge, William H.
      - Tempo
        - Kaylin, Walter
      - Transition
        - [Wilson], Tom
      - Tri-State Record Distributors, Inc. (Box-folder 57/10)
        - Donohue, Mike
      - U.S. Department of Commerce: Bureau of the Census (Box-folder 57/11)
        - Burgess, Robert W.
      - United State Information Agency
        - Eisenstadt, Evelyn
      - Vancouver Boys' Club Association
        - Smith, Bob
      - Vogue Productions Internationales Phonographiques
        - Delaunay, Charles
      - WCAM Bureau of Broadcasting
        - Roberts, Tom
      - WCKY Radio
        - Dale, Rex
      - WDGO-FM Radio
        - Ferguson, Thomas M.
      - Web Distributing Co., Inc.
        - Bathgate, Walter E.
      - Weiss Rhythm and Rhyme Shop
        - [no individual specified]
      - WERE Radio
        - McLean, Phil
      - WFAH Radio
        - Williamson, Don
      - WIIT Radio
        - Joseph, Harry
      - Willis Music Co. of Cleveland
        - Trumbles, Bruce Z.
      - WJQS Radio
        - Garrett, Jack
      - WOOO Radio
        - Gilbert, Jim
      - WOR Radio
        - Koss, Ernest E.
      - WPEO Radio
        - Scott, Ken
      - WQBC Delta Broadcasting Co.
        - Garrett, Jack
      - WSME York Broadcasting Co.
        - Carlson, John
      - WSSO Radio
        - Garrett, Jack
      - WWDC Radio
        - Conover, Willie
    - Correspondence Received: Individuals (Box-folder 57/12)
      - Anderson, Eric
      - Arseneault, Jack
      - Berendt, Joachim E.
      - Bergman, Cadet G.T.
      - Bernard, Allan
      - Boucher, Brian G.
      - Brautigam, Anders
      - Broadneaux, Ulysses B., Jr. (Box-folder 57/12)
      - Carr, Ray
      - Carroll, Harold F.
      - Casteels, Raymond
      - Cholinski, Henryk Z.
      - Clark, Arnold B.
      - Colmer, Bob
      - Coluzzi, Nelson
      - Conover, Willis
      - Conyers, Carl
      - Cory, Raymond L.
      - Crawford, Edward
      - Dale, Brian
      - Darby, Sherman
      - Dennis, John
      - Díaz, Frank, Jr.
      - DiVenuto, Henry
      - Divok, Joe
      - Dorsey, Dean J.
      - DuBois, Stephen C.
      - Feilich, Al
      - Fiorito, Edward
      - Fleiss, Marcel
      - Fogel, Max
      - Gannon, Rob (Box-folder 57/13)
      - Gary, Louis W.
      - Gauguin, Jam
      - Gleason, Ralph J.
      - Gregory, Jack
      - Harlund, T.
      - Henninger, Fred A.
      - Kantor, Frederick I.
      - Kingland, James, Jr.
      - Kirkwood, J.
      - Krügel, Karl Heinz
      - Larmay, Lou
      - Lawson, Kathy
      - Lengsfelder, H.F.
      - Manning, Don (Box-folder 57/14)
      - Mingo, Leonard
      - Morgan, Alun
      - Moss, Bennie
      - Nelson, Beatrice
      - O'Brien, Neil C.
      - O'Connor, Father Norman J.
      - Oglesby, Rufic C.
      - Parker, Chan
      - Parker, Doris
      - Parrish, J.G.
      - Patton, William Y.
      - Purlongo, Bob
      - Raeburn, Boyd (Box-folder 57/15)
      - Roach, Max (Box-folder 57/15)
      - Rubins, Helen
      - Sandridge, Billie
      - Seilagy, Bob
      - Sewell, John W.
      - Shaffer, Dr. J.R.
      - Slocum, Beverly
      - Smith, F.T.
      - Soucie, Gary A.
      - Stith, June D.
      - Summarrisse, Bob
      - Thorstad, Nils
      - Uriesess, C. (Box-folder 57/16)
      - Waldorf, O.D.
      - Walker, R.A.
      - Watton, Dick
      - Zalasnick, Charles
    - Correspondence Sent: Corporate (Box-folder 57/17)